Sue Silva



suelenregsilva@gmail.com



(647)619-7726



linkedin.com/in/suelen-silva-66863693



https://github.com/suersil

Summary

Knowledge of technologies such as HTML, CSS and JavaScript;

Advanced proficiency with AdobePhotoshop, Affinity Photo;

Exposure to customer service (4+years) in a highly collaborative and fast-paced environment;

Strong analytical communication, organization, conflict resolution, problem-solving and time management skills; Leadership and ability to work independently;

Portuguese-English bilingual.

Experience



Web Content Editor

NIBO Distribution - Smoke Vape

Jan 2023 - Present (3 months)

- Made edits to build out pages on the company's WordPress website;
- · Theme and plugin installations;
- Management of the online store, user's posts, reviews and requests;
- · Posting new content, images and products for sales;
- · Editing and creating product photos, and banners using Photoshop, and Affinity Suit.

Receptionist

Silva Dental Lab

Dec 2021 - Feb 2023 (1 year 3 months)

- · Answered and directed incoming calls using a multi-line telephone system;
- Greeted and directed visitors to appropriate personnel and answered average calls and emails daily;
- · Utilized active listening skills to quickly resolve problems;
- · Sorted incoming mail and directed to correct personnel each day;
- Maintained daily calendars, scheduled and confirmed appointments;
- · Followed deadlines and managed priorities daily tasks;
- Updated databases and Labnet system to promote access to information;
- Organized and filled company documents electronically & through a paper filing system.

5]...

Assistant Team Leader

Dollarama L.P.

Jan 2020 - May 2021 (1 year 5 months)

- Provide continuing resolution of customer service, support and assistance conflicts;
- Led and directed store associates performing cashiering, customer service and sales;
- Trained 10+ new team members:
- Delegated daily tasks to associates to optimize group productivity;
- · Completed daily cash reconciliation, closing store and running POS system;
- Created and distributed monthly reports to management regarding performance;

• Received and processed product returns and coordinated disposal of defective or broken items.

Assistant Management

Espaco Pet

Jul 2016 - Oct 2019 (3 years 4 months)

- Answered incoming telephone calls to provide store, products and services information;
- Arranged new merchandise with signage and appealing displays to encourage customer sales and move overstock items;
- Responsible for checking inventory and ordering supplies and merchandise when they reached critical levels:
- Monitored sales and submitted records of store expenses for taxation purposes;
- Responsible for financial organization accounts payable and receivable;
- · Monitored social media activity (Facebook).

Administrative Assistant

Tempo Presente Corretora

Jan 2015 - Mar 2016 (1 year 3 months)

- · Contacted new and existing customers to discuss product and service solutions;
- Generated marketing letters to prospects on behalf of sales representatives to attract new clients;
- Assisted manager with new projects and implemented methods to improve sales efficiency;
- · Participated in daily meetings strategies:
- Reviewed and prepared sales spreadsheets to organize and secure sales records;
- Responded to customer inquiries and offered quality support to resolve sales-related issues;
- Negotiated prices, terms of sale and service agreements to help close new transactions.

Education



Web Development Bootcamp, Computer Programming by: Dr.Angela Yu

Licenses & Certifications

EF SET English Certificate - EF Standard English Test (EF SET) 9r4C3N

(A) Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp

Introduction to Programming Using Java - Ada Tech

Skills

Java • Trello • Affinity Photo • WordPress • Microsoft Office • Adobe Photoshop • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML • JavaScript